inbxx.com 2015-06-26

# Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY 

This Privacy Policy is effective as of January 14, 2014. 

Brainteck respects the privacy of our users and has developed this Privacy Policy to demonstrate its commitment to protecting your privacy. As an individual using our website, we encourage you to read this Privacy Policy very carefully when using our websites or services or conducting business with us. By using our websites, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please refer to the end of this Privacy Policy for information on how to contact us. 

**Information Collected**

Brainteck may collect from you both identifying and non-identifying personal information through our websites or other manner. 

_Information provided by you._ Brainteck may require that you provide certain information to use the services on our site. You may always decline to give any personal information requested by Brainteck, but without the presentation of such information, Brainteck may not be able to provide services to you. 

_Cookies_ . When you visit Inbxx.com, we may assign your computer one or more cookies, to facilitate access to our websites, to personalize your online experience, and to record information about your visit to our websites. Through the use of a cookie, we also may automatically collect information about your online activity on our websites, such as the web pages you visit, the links or advertisements you click, or the other actions you conduct while visiting Inbxx.com if you have enabled cookies. 

_IP Address._ Inbxx.com automatically collects your IP address, access times, and the referring website address for identification purposes. 

_Personal Information_ . This website does not collect, save or store any personal information from visitors that simply browse this website, unless you voluntarily and intentionally provide it to us. We do not collect personal information without your knowledge or consent. 

_Embedded Advertisements._ Advertisements displayed on Brainteck’s web sites may be delivered via an advertising management service. When you view a web page on our web site that contains advertising provided one of our advertising management services, the advertising service company may place a cookie on or retrieve a cookie from your computer if you have enabled cookies. 

_User Communications._ Users of Inbxx.com may from time to time contact Brainteck with inquiries or requests. Brainteck will retain these communications in order to process and respond to these inquiries and requests. 

**Disclosure of Information**

Brainteck may disclose your information: (1) in response to a subpoena, court order, or a request for cooperation from law enforcement agencies; (2) to defend against legal claims; (3) when we believe disclosure is appropriate in connection with efforts to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activity, fraud or wrongdoing; (4) to protect the rights, property, and safety of our company, users, employees or others; (5) to enforce our website terms; (6) in the event of a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of our business, merger, or consolidation; or (7) as otherwise required by law. 

Brainteck reserves the right to share non-personally identifiable information and aggregated data (e.g., anonymous usage data, platform types, referring/exit URLs, etc.) with third parties. 

_**The previous paragraphs notwithstanding, Brainteck will not disclose your information, and uses all of the information collected solely for analytical purposes connected to the operation of the website.** _

**Protection of Your Information**

We take appropriate security measures (including physical, electronic and procedural measures) to help safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access and disclosure. Access to your personal information is restricted to Brainteck’s employees, contractors, and agents, for whom the information is necessary to maintain and improve our services. 

Users should also take care with how they handle and disclose their personal information. 

**Children Accessing Our Web Site Or Products**

We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13 and our products and website are not intended for the use of such children. Should it be revealed to us that we have inadvertently collected information from children under the age of 13, then we will take reasonable measures to eliminate such data from our servers. 

**Modification of this Privacy Policy**

Brainteck reserves the right to, and may from time to time, make changes to this privacy policy. 

Additionally, if you have any concerns about security on Inbxx.com, you can email us at [support@brainteck.com](mailto:support@brainteck.com) with any questions.
